And ride on it, like jay-z, let's look at jay-z on Jeff
Well, that's what I will do I swear if tonight we find $200,000 I will buy a jet ski
I'm hungry too. I got some bubble tea tonight. Um
Look forward to working with the security community. No, I swear I'll buy a jet ski, all right
Okay, so
Where I would kind of look for vulnerabilities here, oh by the way, please subscribe to my shit
I'm not gonna make $200,000. I need your money from twitch
Please please give me money. Oh poor I need any rice
Fans off the fan off
See like my feet are cold
My arms are warm
No, my arms are cold too. But I want the fan. All right
Let's say do we have sound to sound work good sound or excited good
Let's feel we can find
What we are dealing to find is a place where I market isn't validated
They do like they label it like shady market generally
Looking for bugs for a bit. I don't really think I'm gonna find anything
Yeah, we use sublime to read code and I use them to write code pimple my arm I
Live in the same house will come AI guess who would live at work just savage
Alright guys, what do I want over eats? Ooh
North Beach pizza. Oh, yeah a homemade flatbread breadstick. Is that what I want?
Cheese pizza. Is that what I want to see P?
Mmm Oh Sasha's Pakistani restaurant. Whoo that seems kind of good food chicken tikka masala. That's what I want
Yeah
Get that chicken tikka masala
And that's what we're talking about. All right
Is that healthy guys?
Please order. All right. We got some Pakistani food coming
too AM
Is he jumping off a yacht this is real shit or is this meme shit?
This rollercoaster
Yeah
All right, all right guys I know we got work to do tonight
So we're gonna make $200,000 and then we're gonna buy a jet ski, yeah
Wait, we should put jet ski in the title. Maybe we'll get more likes and clicks and views and shit
We'll buy jet ski if win
All right, cool
All right. So what we have to find oh
Man, I wish it with syntax highlight here. That's kind of shitty
So you see this market is legit call
Like this is not this is I would say poorly rigged like they're very careful. Some of them have market as legit calls
There's no reason you can't have a market as legit call here
But they don't do it for some reason. So that's generally like not the best practice. I guess you don't wanna waste gas
So, okay, let's let's look into this only whitelisted call this thing
Let's see if there's ever a way we're gonna be able to bust that
Know these things are just whitelisted by the control wire. That's all order has this contract called it can scatter. What auger is it's a
Decentralized prediction market platform built on a theory. Oh, that's right
Well, my friends works there and I told them look at security, but it's actually extremely good
So there's all this like forking crap
I'm not sure like how useful it is like I
Worry that there aren't shallow bugs that there's just like extremely deep bugs
That would take weeks to find and we don't have weeks. The Karger is launching soon
No, but we got to stop with the pessimism we got to start believing in myself and you know, what else
I wish I had some damn chapstick
Stick
Weed pen check it a crazy dream today guys took a nap
Chapstick no chapstick
Come on relaxation supports learning ability. Here's my theory are they allowed to say that shit that seems it legal?
Delicious vitamin alright
So these are the libraries
Is this like its own contract that gets deployed should read the deployment code
I
Think it's mostly just gonna be a reading code. You can zoom in. Whoa. Let's see you guys can see better
Universe create yes, no more. This is how markets get created and just look at the universe
I cashed a nomination to
Market factory create market value
So this stuff always makes me excited because
like
It looks like I can create a market. They're calling it I cash but it looks like I can create a market with anything
So remember that if you don't actually check it I can pass in any contract here that doesn't actually have to behave like any RC
Use 'fl that is though
The market
Yeah, okay so see it's useless the idea of like passing in something weird here is useless because it doesn't look up with the controller
The great thing is though since we're attacker is we only need to find one bad thing
Contribute
That for create dispute crowdsource, er
If there's any way - like shoving something here that isn't actually a
Disavow crowdsources see okay. So it's this kind of bullshit
I wonder if there were bugs like deeper in the etherium platform that we can think about
There's little you could do to a contract
The whole order would fall apart if we could get one
Malicious contract in like the trusted stuff, right?
Does the whole a theory of security model is is weird to think about?
By the way
I'm telling you 24 are you're watching?
If people actually showed up here then this would have to go away because no people can't have nice things
Like this is what I've learned about the world the people used to be able to have nice things
But like now people can't or nice things anymore
Maybe the default
Maybe if they default to call if you're in function what you mean by that so like there's this kind of crap here
Anything the checks deep Oh
Get his address or 0 address shady reporting
What is the zero contract what happens if you try to call the zero contract
Not useful I
Can get that to return anyone but
All right, so this good morning this function here can actually be anything I want
Like it's not really useful
You're not gonna get past this check
You're searching only on the source so you don't get all the testing crap
Now the functions that define them
I
Wish take highlighted this
There's a container for a few went down
Get few window ID return shady few endo equals legit few window
So this isn't gonna work is container for feet
Unfortunately these these is container calls. They're really what I want to attack but they all seem good
If we could attack any of these is container for their things now, I think we might have some lock
Start time shady feeling go get start time. Okay, so we can actually do anything
We want there
Like that, that's the weird stuff to think about
Start time
That's already determined
Like it has to have the address in this feet windows thing
Yeah, and if you assume that checks cry for this checks, correct
Its container for share token is this one bad
Get market, if not is container for more. Okay. Oh
Man, I wish I could get through. This is a container for market check. It's the best one
Legit market
Alright I'll see
Come back to universe in a minute. Oh man. I've really opened a lot of these
Show your 14 participant presents
I don't wanna share this
Participants against as part of the market
so we checked with the shittier boy, which is actually a part of the market as
Well as a crowd sorcerer
See look if we can break this container for market we could like mess with the open interest
That's what I really want to do. So we win two hundred thousand dollars and we get a jetski
Dude I don't know man, that was all bullshit man
Did that sound I talk that was that was during the smoke weed erryday phase man
Does bullshit like you can't really do that
like it good - why if you care I
Get it. Well, I like neuro-link. I don't think really works. I
Don't know anyone might be smarter than that. At least when I talked to him early on about the software having car stuff
I don't think he exactly understood
Like what machine learning was? I think he might now
Really it's not a bandwidth issue and the simple argument to be made about why it's not a bandwidth issue is
Your eyes have so much bandwidth, right? Why can't you read faster?
You'd have to pre-process it
So no, it's not. It's a stupid idea
you know like
Yeah, I probably used to talk with it like more confidence
I probably used to like, you know, I would be able to oh, yeah. Yeah, we'll talk like I know what I'm saying
That's bullshit man. And none anyone else knows that the talking about, you know, a lot of people are real idiots. But oh
No you
Can't you can't stick a high-bandwidth pipe into the brain that makes no sense
Life advice on the
Switch. Oh
God, I don't know are there even like good bugs in this this probably bugs are the probably really deep. I want shallow bugs
don't want jet ski now I
Will buy a jet ski guys, I will buy a jet ski
Excitable or if it's migrated out function and you could burn and you could pass in any amount that you want to burn something like
whatever
All right, so here's like a nice great one-off check written does that check wrong
You can't be geo hot 2.0 this is dumb idea
You can't be 2.0 of somebody else. You gotta just be 0 to 1
You know
We're gonna press next economy eyebrows
Where my karma shirt
Disgusting. No bike. I'm sure shelter come another. I know this twitch and I don't have to shell
The only reason I stream is so I look less stupid when I talk to myself
Where's my chicken?
You
Oh my mouse works, oh nice did everything working sweet everything's working
Look I have a pink iPad. It's pink
All right
Let's see
I've been bored tonight. I did the triple bite quiz to get a job. Maybe someone will hire me
Yo we go put Ian on a jetski, that's right, no not here talking with coma guy
Okay, so the only thing I was seeing was that I could create another Genesis universe
Like it's again still not really help
If you don't get any control of anything when you create a Genesis universe
Your look I can call create Genesis universe but like it's like useless I
Could control some of these things might be useful
What does parent invalid mean some log
Good child universe
See this can only be called from a market
It's only whitelisted caller things makes things useless and that's just all logging
Which won't actually mess with anything. I mean, it might be broken, but there were actually break auger get me $200,000
Let me tell you something if we find a high-priority bug we only get
$5,000 and that's a shitty jetski compared. Good jetski
Huh
What is only in bad times man
I can pass anything that I want here from market
See how like this has this market as the JIT modifier and then trading ask a patch this one doesn't
No, no, no, we don't look for exploits anymore. I'm doing this for a friend
What can I do with this
Calls this
It doesn't matter cuz this doesn't modify anything notice how they like this isn't good
Jeff Rossen share value your market, so this can be I can pass anything one. There's anything actually call this
contract interfaces
No, no, that's a view I mean they should call it a view because it is a view as far as I can tell
Home get frozen share value
Ooh, but it's not a view because it looks like it does this Nemo eyes frozen shares value. Oh, this is interesting
So what if you can break it lets me my last
Known outcomes
Yeah, oh this is interesting
Well, so what is the key that it uses to mean a lot uses a market key it might not be useful
Yeah, okay it looks like it uses a market key so it isn't useful I
Think yeah, I mean there's no way to spoof that
No just be zero for my fake market, okay, that's not that useful
Market outcome frozen share value
Yeah, I'll be cool theta and I should have the market there
Yeah, I know. They're offering a good bounty, right?
We're gonna get back to streaming twitch slam
Some day tomorrow maybe extreme Trish slam tomorrow I
Went to Vegas last weekend, it's pretty awesome
What that I'm streaming who cares
Don't pay me. I don't care about any money except I need money from twitch people
on twitch s yeah, we could go back to church says I saw your contribution to twitch s
We should try we should do more Trish maybe but no what I want what I want to add to twitch slam
Is no I didn't win this. No jetski
But I wanted you for Twitter slams. I want to make a virtual world to test it
I don't want to test on real videos thing where I want to build a goal of rendering little environment
Okay
Alright let's look at all of these ones that take in markets and see if any of them don't enforce that markets are legit
I'm sure that's all right. Just test markets legit
Private this one doesn't
Divide up winnings doesn't check if markets legit. I'll just calculate proceeds
Lots of you so it's not useful
That's not useful right there
Let just divide up winnings I
Mean it's not a view
Why isn't this one of you
Oh
Wow responsible disclosure, here's my middle fingers. No, it's not live yet. I wouldn't do this for live
Their launch date is uh
I'll say I wanna scare
Ya July nice so they have two days
But this is also my feelings about responsible disclosure, I think you might feelings about responsible anything
Oh, wait, is it at the top of hm, really?
See my nature
God like dude
They should ban. I would love to see a ban of
all
like news
Like no no the Guardian no, New York Times no Wall Street Journal. No
Chicago Tribune, no Reuters. Hell no
Hacker news without any links to mainstream news. Oh
So Java zero, I love them people job zero des man
Did the worldly
Love me. It's more Anarchy
nothing everything in balance, but more Anarchy would uh
Kind of be nice. Okay, so why is this not a view?
Get more cash reporting fee divisor. So
It's only universe
So check that the deaths under their cash before you device
Good current he wouldn't know get her create previous even know
Cut our create timestamp. Oh no
I don't actually know
What um, I mean hacker news is fine as an aggregator, I just I just yeah, I'm just disgusted by like the headlines
The rise of sudo AI how tech firms
Quietly use humans to do BOTS work like I actually this is the one that really disgusts me
Like let's look at the use of the word quietly
Right, like that's not a factual word. That's an agenda pushing word Oh
Using what one it's just disgusting
Quietly
Like this is ways to write things in a much more neutral tone I
Mean that and that's what like I just don't like to see it triggers me, you know. Oh
South Korea has limited no see I'm just disgusted reading this. Never mind. Okay. I can't I can't no
Like I would like for one site to be different
I would like for one community of people to be like
Smart enough to recognize that stuff and then not have and then also to have the UM
What's the word the?
Responsible Ness to avoid being triggered by it Oh
Read it's destroyed all I it's a god
I I want to one read it I go on one subreddit I go on our machine learning. I like our fashion learning, okay
Let's see what's here
Under the great pin post, what are you reading?
How big of a generalist are you like this is this is just good
She like this is awesome
Sorry, I'm getting distract it is hard to read this code
We have a great data set for us at Como
One day two separate areas
Me
That's it like there's nothing offensive this subreddit there's nothing offensive about it
Yeah, probably I wish I just wish hacker news was more like that and there is still some good content on there
And to keep triggered seeing the bad content I
Mean it's it's just it's what's scaring the Internet apart. I googled something. I googled something I was looking for I googled like
It was an old concept. It was like when sports stars burn outs. I remember reading something about it years ago
So, oh, yeah. I was googling private search engines. So I googled like sports star burn out
and it's just
shit
Like legally late like
Want to be a sports star don't specialize the young star when athletes decide the thrill is gone like oh my god. I
would love to see
What this used to be I would love to see what Google looked like in in 2012 and then sorry, you know
I went to doctor go and I was like, okay these people any better. Um,
No, and it's it's the same shit
Look, they even have news like come on DuckDuckGo. Like I don't care about your privacy shit. I just wish they would give me like
I mean, I would rather eat Oh see like this is interesting
I love archive
Interesting, but this is fascinating right like like like like wow
This is something nice
And I mean, this is something yeah, this is something I probably would have would have thought beforehand
in the NBA
All the talent is of the Golden State Warriors of LeBron and baseball and hockey are pretty random
That's why they have to play so many games. Oh
My foods almost here sweet
um
But yeah, I mean look this is like interesting. Alright, I wish yeah
But I wish I wish the internet was more like this. I wish was the content more people wanted
To get my chicken tikka masala with my grown on
With ubers here who's running out of here. Yeah. I hate when they do this. They're like, oh we're gonna go downstairs
We know how long it takes you there that the algorithm you have fuck your algorithms
And then we're gonna go back to auditing order
What is that oh
Nice oh, this is this is good old good old good old finding them whereas FTPS because the internet used to be cool
Ah food
No, yo, bro, yeah when you go home do it a thousand dollars, so I'm going to a femoral necks tweaked my
elbow
Ha ha yeah got that garlic naan
Back to auditing order
Tentative winning. Oh, yeah, we're ready for press of course
Who lose all spicy hmm
I read this universe one a lot. Like this is where I'd be really excited to find the exploit because it would be good. I
Can't buy Jeff D for a $5,000
How I don't you secure it anymore slop bullshit
fathers like breathing
You might not even be about
No marketable
Gent where cash
I mean on stuff that doesn't even have a name
Points look a batter far
Yeah, lift up the auger bug bounty program we're looking for anything worth $200,000
What's an I mailbox
What's a delegation target, let's figure this out
I'm telling target is controlled
Yeah just means they have this control arm and
I'm also excited about complete sets. This does seem like way too much logic to handle complete sets
No, if I get a hundred CAD reports that to five K's on ones were blaring
Allen to $5,000 bounty programs lose five acres
It's not hack this hacker one, uh
Make probably big thing. I wanna
Know did they not give me a fork
Hey, don't give me a fork. I don't know why they give me a fork. Ah
Fork I was like a sporky thing
So
What's a delegator
Do these factories have any special permissions
I would doubt
We have linked to the
Universe in some way because otherwise, how are they doing universe? I
Have to pass in the universe. Okay, it looks like they don't have any special permissions at all
What other report
Not rip this apart
This report is extremely good
It's also not that many lines of code
Let's really commit history
No
Oh fix some issues now
A minor can manipulate the gas reporting bond
They only got $5,000 that's not enough
Like I said, we have to be able to buy a jet ski
My Tesla's down and so I'll talk about
Wow, you should pull
Logic removed
Let's go up on Tesla, we're all oh
You know, let's listen to push a tease album even though we're getting copyrights I haven't listened to it yet. It was my release radar
I don't know man. Mrs. Drake had a kid
Drake named named one of his songs after the day his kid was conceived
I
Just like I have listened to this
Broken new dick time body
The copper please a mess with my computer
What someone hacking my spot
Nevermind they don't want me to play the copyright police came after me. Oh my god
I don't know. What would
Classic classic guile online, you know, I ain't saw him and use that against
I
Was not doing
Alright I'll say what I've acted Melissa Ling Joe
She calls me
Harder than the government
Bro
If I had some Alvin you believe, you know a good day chicky chicky saw in honor
There's this thing called the back
It's actually like this song doesn't lie if I had the Carter five
I've you and you're organized that guy if Joe Rogan would have me while I go on
You better have a rule if I going any shows it's no politics
Politics is the mind come
And talk about Louis the 15th during the French Revolution
Oh
No, I really want the girl shallow bugs in this I'm gonna kick myself when someone finds one now
And why am I auditing I
Wanna say this is dumped and I really planted $200,000
I should audit some aetherium code that's like never been audited that has just two hundred thousand dollars of eats sitting in it
There's so much money to be made doing this shit pros
Don't actually want a jet ski
Guys, if I actually got a jet ski, I really want you to think about what a hassle that would be. Okay, so
I'm not sure you can park the jet ski on land
Like I probably to be honest need a trailer for my jet ski now
and now we're gonna leave my trailer with a jet ski somewhere I
Could take it up. Am I just allowed to take a jet? Ski and go?
to the beach
We've really you stood it up ugly chest. That's awesome
that is
Nope, it's not. I made a lot of money. It's that I
Don't spend money on anything. I mean like okay, I spend like 30 bucks a day on food
But
Okay, you can actually wait let's let's go delete s and let's play trick stuff
I'm copying and pasting
Can I play it it only loses I
Can watch it I can look at its games
Might play against it
There with the machine, come on, wait, how do I challenge someone li chess?
Can I challenge the bot just sign up
Hate that
Oh
This is too hard
Alright fine real email at gmail.com. We need to don't tell me I need like to farm at
This is the worst oh
Sweet oh god, I don't get confirmed shit. Okay, I can I challenge it
Challenge to again, let's go
Real-time
And outside
Challenge declined
Let's bounce back
Enter your email. Oh
Wait, how come twitch chests declines my challenge?
No, I want to play twitch chess challenge to a game maybe it's because I set like stuff
Unlimited
Size
It's gonna make me want to improve twitch chess. Yeah. I really don't think I'm gonna find anything casually reading me clothes like this
When I find something I don't gotta do shit man because I'm real
This is America a huge American flag over there. I love America and I love freedom and I didn't got to do shit
And that's the true fact about everything anybody who tells you that you God you shit they're lying, this is America
It doesn't work I
Hate this
Has experience on shrews or acid don't talk about that here guys
Maybe it only wants to play rated
Damn and we have rooms mass in America. They're like legal here. Now. That's a lie
But you know, it's America we have freedom
Superleague, oh, man
Everything is legal like no the thing about America is like everything's illegal
But like it doesn't matter because who respects the law nobody
Because they made all these stupid laws against like drugs and shit and made nobody respectful law
They're watering to have the cannabis I have experienced this
You so good. Yeah. Yeah, I think the legal shit's a little bit worse than the medical shit I used to get
You know leach s works fine, but can I challenge twitch s to a game
Okay, if someone wants to challenge me blahblah 121 and you want to play it you want to play fast I'll play it
I'll play a five-minute game against um
So I want to challenge you right now you'll probably beat me
I'm blahblah 121
This is check correct required token
The universe get beyond universe
I'm the child universe
Yeah, that checks good put this one
Long doesn't reach parameter
Someone challenged me
Mumbai shower copies. Oh
Yeah, let go
We go with the King's pawn opening follow it up with the
Denied - right here. Oh
That's the ready attack. Oh, we're in a real Oh pens. Oh, I love the we Lopez. Oh
Yeah, I know that that's the morphe defense. We'll take the night
Yeah, thank you for your pawn good sir
Oh, he's attacking me retreat
Let's see, they should exchange
No, bishop exchange council King Schneider cleans that and I looks like the actually only Kingston will go there
Good castle sir good castle. All right
There yeah, I can't tell you guys my strategy because whoever this is might be watching this this chess
Oh, yeah, look at that freak on love it. Ah
The old retweet retreat the Queen but now this pawn is free to I believe
Yeah, ah
The old Knight attacks the Queen problem
Mmm, yeah, we might not be able to come home
Mmm there just go there
There
Oh, okay. Well now that's being uh, yeah
They're playing defensive play defensive guys. Oh
Let me check it make this throw bros, I didn't think this through oh
I thought you were gonna attack that. Okay, we're gonna take that. I just gave you ideas queen
Ah
The old retreat the Queen I love that one. Oh, yeah marks with the pause push push push push
Push push
Yeah every pawn
Bro that was a bad movie this gave me a rock. I
Think oh, well, I'm actually to throw I was eating
Hmm what that goes
Right, we gotta play a little faster half
Goes no one knows when the Batcave closed ah
The attack of that, I don't care you take that
No, oops
Hello and welcome back
Why'd you do that bro, I
Mean take that it's fine. I didn't want it to begin with
That's what I wanted to do
Yeah, well
Yeah, resign o'clock good game bro
The nine-year-old you're losing jiwan's is one minutes back. Yeah
I'm embarrassing the bad Chester G
Let's play the bye
No Oh
Who's this unlimited now alright pot doesn't work broken
Are we giving up are we giving up on auger guys I
Don't have any ideas about where to look let's just go through every contract and take a look at those bugs there
Can't call initialize twice
Those are gonna have any special authority
Let's see who gets let's check the contract employer and see who gets whitelisted
Weightless trading contractors
I'll do a five minute challenge. Okay, last one. I'll try
Cuz I did create the account which was a lot of effort
Time control. Oh, yeah
Oh
Don't work let that keep going and maybe it'll work I
Said trading. Oh
Yeah, let's go twitch chess
All right, you're white you go first
Please be nice on the chess I've ever met the Internet. What a stupid move. Well his pot sauce
Wow, this pot really sucks. I
Lost my second clean. Oh, no good thing was my second Queen
Will it take my queen. Oh, no, it took my queen. Oh, that was a good move, but this bot is so bad
Wow it knew how to put me in shit. Well that was actually pretty good move. Oh, never mind, you know
Unbelievably dumb
Yeah checkmate bitch
Oh chicken tikka masala kind of nasty
Nope
Yeah, b201 that was how well it played chess
All right things to do improve twitch chess
Did alphago complete my asset go I'm pretty bad at go
I bet even the old the old non neural things could be my asset gal
Alright so everything that's called trading apparently. Oh
These these are all trusted
These are white listed contracts
Well
Well, I may be sure that means
Okay, so what if I mess with that
I don't really think that's like useful like
Hmm
Okay, alright, so here's what I'm thinking guys this is a whitelisted contract
This would record are some interesting shit for it to work for like okay for example, like take a look at this one here, right?
Well, no, okay, we have to look out let's understand how the message sender works
Like eat all that not pass out any that monster it looked one serving
Now movies foods nasty then add that a pizza that I ate disgusting food
Sender of the message so
Can change for every
External function call okay, so this doesn't actually have to be a market
That can actually be a
So I can call contracts that say like whitelisted only
From there assuming that this is a
Yeah, like dot get universal this is actually done with a hash
There might just be no collisions here, but you see what I'm saying I
Don't know if anyone knows anything about aetherium. Correct me if I'm wrong
But like I passed something else in here. It's a contract that like it's like the like which contract like every other contract
You know, where's the one that like lets you is that a market contract
There's one unless you just manipulate open interest if you're a market
Or if you're white list
Only white list of callers
Controller a searches whitelisted message center. Okay, so this is probably
Trusted
No sir, it is white listed
Yeah, it's fine
So it'd be added to the white list so now if we're on the white list of their cool things we can do I
Think more than white list. We're just entirely trusted
Market you never
See like I like this one because it's not well
does that even matter its marked as a view but
Ah
Okay
So be fine if they were views, but like this one's not a few. So this calculate reporting fee will actually let me call
arbitrary things on a contract
Assuming they have the same hash as get universe
But unfortunately, whatever it returns will actually also have to be contract Oh
So this, okay
I can I can make this a contract I control this market contract then I can call Margaret get universe on it and
I could pass in any address there. So I just need to find something that collides with
Get or cash reporting fee divisor
That's white listed
now
enough to dig into the theory maybe I
to figure out
Who this shit works though, you see what I'm saying? Who understands the exploit? I don't know man. That's probably not an exploit
This is so this can this can return any contract I want and
the message dot sender
Will be this claim trading proceeds
Now we just need to find a collision, okay, so
We would need to find a collision in the name space with a getter cache reporting fee divisor
With something that's only whitelisted callers
Safari see if there's anything cool you can do if you're a while s good call
Oh wow
It looks like you can do anything, okay, Eddie I hash
No, that's too much effort
Wow
Just going online thing for this city I - online cake Oh
Useless
If I recall correctly, yeah, that's not right. Is it the other
Okay Webster here sweet
Sweet
Making my life easy. Ah
So the function I can call from is here
It's a few so fucking a work I can certainly call this
Alright
What JavaScript
Yeah
That's a lot to collide
No, no either for you fuck off
Yeah, so there was something colliding with that
So way for me to get control over that but like
It's not really an exploit
We would have to make it seem like it came from this contract
Message that sender will be this contract. So this is an external call
Market don't get universe. Well, actually we can let's see what that actually is
Directions a tie universe
Checking my universe it has this crap
So some functions are each other you inch that doesn't matter those returns really matters. I don't know
You don't want to read the actual assembly that it outputs
Sioux City nice out of that guy's been a while stuck down this
Alright so I was attacking this clam trading proceeds like
This one didn't know
Well isn't gonna compile
This there's no definition of highmarket
Let's get I mortgage. Oh
You get universe function and charge our universe no, you're not universe -
So I type tell me just like check something
No, this is stupid get type name function, that's great
Hi
What expected pragma import or contrast what
Was the problem
Remember div visible all because I'm not using out, okay
Alright already call them. That's fine
Okay, cool
Unused function parameter I had something called a mount. I don't know
After this compiles, can I see the assembly?
I'll go here Oscar VM
Oh my god, I
Don't need that
No, they're gonna Twitter kay, I have it on good authority
P.m. Error vert
Debug the transaction to get more information. Well good. There's what I wanted to begin with. Okay
This is total crap
Okay
So that's the call to market to get universe we can confirm that
About three years well
Yeah universe
Yeah, so notice how this number here matches
Those off-screen number down here this number here
They do match that's good. So exciting
Shorty em low. Oh-oh-oh size zero
Alright, so there's a call to physic call see the stack
That's your shall we
I can't use Ida for this call data
What's horseshit I
Have an idea guys, I don't know if any of this works doesn't work. I probably shouldn't tell you all about it. I
Mean where's the retard
You'd have to very carefully corrupt the stack
I'm not really sure you can do it
We require diving deep into the etherium vienna
But it's a cute idea
We're way over tax code size
Of the coded address a
Interesting
It's the address where let's go back to where we did they call
The clothes the coolest thing we did
Okay, cool gasp call
You can't believe you know, what bro
You
Are banned that's right
That's right a
Little bit just ignored no, no, no, but like
We want to ban this user. Oh, there we go. Mod user
Timeout user yeah, everything bad for that. Oh, no, not moderator
No, that's not what I want. What why the hell I do that timeout user
Yeah the same get banned
Now he's not a moderate but don't worry
You had the words moderator ever for like seconds good vibes only gross vibes only
Actually, no if this works
Point doesn't know so that's the cause is that to call to get universe?
I
Think it is I think this is it actually
It's this
She's actually very interesting
Um, I
Think uh very call. Yeah I get universes this
It's that so
It's here
Call eBay
Okay
Call up go has gas to value. You know, I've set out offset outsides
That's gasps address transaction value
Gasps to value
In offset in size out offset out size that makes sense because we're only sending four
Yeah
That's really gonna work because
An offset out size
Know what doing block stream shit fuck block stream
um, I mean, I think it up to get extremely I
Don't know I don't think this works I think you have to get extremely lucky
Debtor cash
Important fee divisor
Now we're not hacking anything actually I cut it I can't I kind of regret doing any hacking I
Don't know bros never looting twitch s tomorrow, it's not fun. This is fun. Fuck this I don't need money I
Think this might work so we should look into it. You see what I'm saying?
You understand kind of what the game is
Boys I don't actually need money dis regardless in the next twitch Street when I'm begging you all for money
Because I want my food twitch, okay
money
See look guys look look at all the money. I got I got I got a dollar. I got two dollars. I got $2
dollars
Rich
But no, no the jet ski will be at nightmare. No
Somebody else you know, what? How about this take this idea? I think it works like you see the idea, right?
You'll get message sender to be yours Center is set - uh-huh. This was the Evie my paper
No, no the one that like goes into like this shit
Yeah
This goes into the holy video
Basically wanna know if the call off code sets message sender
Async call
Wow that looks like exploits waiting to happen
DVM shellcode
I
Do I do on a way I don't know I don't care
Maybe I'll work for tomorrow privately. I
Don't like finding exploits in front of people
No, but here's what it is guys know what you know, why you know what you know, what's really wrong
The stuff don't of this twitch channel is supposed to be utterly and completely useless
And
The problem is this
verges on the edge of useful like this might actually be relevant because guys
Look, do you really want to contribute to the world?
Really?
It's overrated
You want to have skill and talent and then not contribute because that's funny
That's funny
Think of the opposite of funny somebody who like is
Passionately committed to causes. Oh, oh
Passionately committed to causes. Oh, that's not funny
No hate money
Yeah, I know I know you have to get the money in there now on it now, you know what
Care what people think about a thought about me but now I like dough. I don't care. I can't do it. It's too hard
It's impossible guys can't do it. It's too hard
Core of the first function to be called inside the current contract scope
Just the our contract that it just becomes the message center
Yes, this does work in theory with the message senders, yeah, well maybe I figured it out everybody I'm gonna mm ah, so are you
Wait, this fuckers back. No way
Wait, how was he back?
No, no he can't be back
ban user
Perfect. Now he's gone
Come back
No, he's not a mod no, no, he's not
Yeah, dude, let's see everyone's doing with the Malaysian kids I heard about that base deal ah, bro
Alright so who sees the exploit it's right there just diplomat that. Oh, no, so what you have to
Mmm, I
Mean you get this nice call to set up the stack. However you want
You have to somehow manipulate the stack such that that call probably goes to a different
Set of bytes
And I think
my understanding
Is is it would be out of bounds if you tried to call I mean, are there any good functions we can call in these?
only whitelist callers with I
Think it would seg fault line. I try to read that
Oh
But that's just man this is beautiful
Not a mod
All right
How's exploit
This whole whitelist things bad I think oh no, I
Always be tired guys. I guess I guess I can't do it. I guess I guess I'm auditing. I guess that's impossible
Oh, yeah, that's right. It's impossible a hacking auger is 100% completely impossible and
Yes, try to implement this tomorrow. I would be very happy if somebody beat me to it
And took the $200,000 for themselves
But
No, I haven't done it I told you everything I know like I think this works I
Think that you just have to be like particularly clever in the implementation of it
200 kgs chump change absolutely. She could really manipulate open interest
No guys no nyet don't learn Java guys technology sucks of technologies evil
What's body yachts?
Almost like 200 yards. Yeah, exactly just by yawns bad
Spy. Yeah Wow
All right
I'm gonna lie in bed and stare at this more
But I don't think it's appropriate. I don't think we have that kind of relationship where you can come into bed with me
The world is a beautiful place. I'm so happy
Active launch a no no, this is the only time I regret ever I've never had logic again. I'm putting this shit away
I'm not looking at any more. It's stupid. It's stupid guys
you could you could you could waste your life thinking you're gonna make money and then you could have money and
You know what? We're gonna leave with
Ya
You do know that he was shot right and if he didn't have money no one would shop
I'm your host for the day mace Gumbel with this last Brodie
I've never actually watch this video before
Just cost shit to code in the closet someone's got to pay my overeat spell though just steal credit cards
Just kidding don't steal credit cards kids. It's illegal laws matter
I
Don't know I've never seen
Just kidding just kidding. This is my commitment that we're done. We're not hacking anymore shit. Oh, yeah, please I need donations, please
Please please the fake money to me. I love you donate money
Donate money for the prom banning of that guy who came in here talk shit
Bolcom a happy word three commas. I don't know shit about money. I'm sure yourself self-driving cars sounds kind of fun, right?
Donate money stop with it. You'll piss me off effective altruism Oh,
Rationalists Oh
, artists with the shitty peppers
What you know the kind that like claims they're artists but actually worship Starbucks of that kind of heart
The kind who like like like barista or a latte artist. I'm that kind of artist, right?
Say scream chest I did win both my chess games a
Sandwich artist yeah, that's what I'm talking about. I'm that kind of artist
All right, that's the end of the song alright guys I will
See you all tomorrow, maybe Christmas wicks-lim maybe bye-bye